CJ ENM CO., LTD. PRESENTS
A HIVE MEDIA CORP. PRODUCTION
Christmas we've all been waiting
for is just around the corner.
I feel empty inside having
spent another uneventful year.
Why don't magical things
ever happen to me?
It's cold and nothing is going my way.
I hope we get a lot of snow.
This letter was sent by a listener.
If everything in life went as
planned, what fun would that be?
Don't magical things
happen when least expected?
I'll sing the song you
requested to cheer you up.
♪ Jingle bell, jingle bell, ♪
♪ jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a ♪
♪ one-horse open sleigh, yeah! ♪
♪ Jingle bell, jingle bell, ♪
♪ jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a ♪
♪ one-horse open sleigh, yeah! ♪
Yes, sir.
Yes, that's confirmed.
HAN JI MIN
Winter Festival meeting
will commence at 3,
Art Fair meeting at 5,
LEE DONG WOOK
and the Gingerbread Charity
is underway without a hitch
Yes, I'll keep you in the loop.
KANG HA NEUL
LIM YOON A
I know you're all busy during
this full-booking season.
WON JIN A
We need to be focused!
Yes!
LEE HYE YOUNG
Also, the CEO's boiler froze
up, so it's being repaired.
He'll be staying here
in the suite for a while.
JUNG JIN YOUNG
KIM YOUNG KWANG
SEO KANG JUN
LEE KWANG SOO
KO SUNG HEE
Why not?
I'm better off at a hotel.
LEE JIN UK
No way, tell me which flight,
I'll come pick you up.
I know you have a lot to prepare.
- CHO JUN YOUNG
- I'll contact you once I check in.
WON JI AN
♪ Jingle all the way! ♪
Merry Christmas!
A YEAR-END MEDLEY
Welcome, sir.
I hope madam isn't too
upset for waiting so long.
I can see everyone's
future except for mine.
I'm also clumsy once I leave the hotel.
Wasn't I supposed
to give you a reading?
Yes!
How's later today?
Right here? Today?
Sure, I'll call you once I'm done.
My gosh, thank you!
I'll see you later.
- Okay!
- See you!
Sir, it's here!
Right, I know.
I knew it was here.
Call me.
Afternoon, I'm here.
Another casting call for Lee Gang?
It's written all over your face.
He took over all year-end music charts.
At this rate he won't have time for us.
No way!
You believed in him when no one did.
I think a lot of people
can relate to that.
You know I'm having a
Christmas concert, right?
I sent you two tickets to
enjoy with your family or friend.
I hope you create nice memories
with your loved ones.
I got it.
What?
You'll get a proposal
before the year ends.
Really?
I think you already have an idea.
Not too many days
until the year's over.
Life is always full of surprises.
Everything in even
numbers, always in pairs.
Even serial number
and expiration dates.
Should I leave two of these?
Leave it if it normally
comes in singles.
Make sure to check the serial number.
He's such an odd guy.
I heard he even counts his rice grains.
No way.
Where there's smoke, there's fire.
Audition Call for Musical 'Classic'
Isn't that a really famous musical?
Are you auditioning?
Not really.
I just applied for it a while back.
Better than making
beds here until you die.
No need to clean windows.
It's the boss after all.
That stupid boss will
work us till we drop.
See you later!
♪ I will fly away ♪
♪ Hold your breath and watch me ♪
♪ I'll show you my everything ♪
♪ The real me that was kept away ♪
♪ Run fast! Fly high! ♪
♪ I won't stop again ♪
♪ I'll show you my everything ♪
The real me that was…
Sorry, I thought it was done.
No, sir, I haven't
wiped the windows yet
I heard you were coming.
Sorry for the trouble.
It's okay, I'll be out of your way.
Baek Lee-young?
Very even name.
Thank you.
Enjoy your stay.
Drive safe, sir.
I will.
Do you think it's true that
Ah-young and Yoo-jun are dating?
She's not insane!
There's no way…
No way in hell…
Are you crying?
You're a sharp prick.
Are you crying too, Sae-jik?
Whatever.
Hey, he's only into swimming.
Then I call dibs on her.
I like Ah-young!
What's up with him?
Speak up, idiot.
Come here!
Hello?
- Hae-sun! Wait, hold on.
- Jae-yong.
- Listen to me, don't hang up.
- It's over, don't call me again.
I'll pass the civil service
exam, I promise, please!
One last chance.
Remember what you said?
You said you won't
call me if you fail again!
So why are you calling
me? Just stop it already!
Hae-sun, baby… Why are
you doing this to me?
Oh my…
Please, just once more…
No! No!
Oh no! Come here! Quickly!
Captain, he's here again,
the Saturday blind date man.
I heard he's a plastic surgeon.
You're being nosy.
Well, he's been here over 20 times.
But he gets rejected every time.
I'm just curious.
He's so gorgeous but
keeps getting rejected.
I guess, that's weird.
Not sure.
That's awkward…
I guess he'll be back next week.
He called you by your name?
Maybe he's got a crush on you.
Why would he fall for a
girl wiping his windows?
Why not? Everyone knows
you're the hottest maid.
Not the second hottest?
You're the hottest.
You're so sensible.
Huh? My necklace.
Where did it go?
Necklace?
I saw it earlier, very bling-bling.
Where did it go?
You knocked three times, then once.
Next time, please knock twice.
Four times is good too.
What can I do for you,
Ms. Baek Lee-young?
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't be here.
But I lost something.
Must be very important.
Yes! It's my necklace…
it's really important…
Why don't you come look for it?
It's all right, sir.
My anxiety got the better of me.
I'm so sorry.
It's him!
Careful, careful!
We need to get to the next show!
We'll need to cut short!
Thank you!
Watch your head.
Sorry, sorry, thank you!
Careful, careful!
Thank you!
Get a new manager!
Change your agency!
Take care of him!
Get a new car!
Yeah! Get him a new car!
Please move!
Aren't you tired?
We're on the road constantly,
we should get a better ride.
Hang in there.
We'll pay off the debt soon,
let's go car shopping then.
Hey, Gang.
Producer Na called earlier…
You know I don't do variety shows.
I don't want to say it again.
Okay, I'll reject him.
Get some shut eye.
Kang Sang-gyu!
Yes?
Don't remember me?
Bong-yup.
- Bong-yup?
- Yeah.
- Lee Bong-yup?
How long has it been?
Too long.
How have you been?
I don't go by 'Bong-yup' anymore.
What?
Catherine.
Call me Catherine.
He's so clean.
I hope it's here.
Where could it be?
'Ms. 10020,
I hope this is what
you were looking for.'
Don't call me that.
My name, 'Baek Lee-young.'
Oh, play on words for '100-2-0'?
Our boss has a sense of humor.
That's a relief.
I know, right?
I couldn't even sleep a wink.
Oh my.
Thank you, please let me know if I
can help you with anything - 10020
It's locked.
Wow.
You look pretty, are you in love?
I've always been pretty.
So-jin!
Been a while.
Look who it is.
You're making me sad, you know that?
Why is a single gal
pretending to be so busy?
How can we only meet up once a year?
We used to play 8
days a week as a band.
Anyways, now that you're
here, let me pour you some water.
Hey, go easy.
- She'll be 40 soon.
- And you already are.
Chug it, chug it.
Wow, look at her go.
- You still got it.
- Wow.
See, she's still got it.
You got my respect.
- Empty the glass.
- Nice.
We're going for round 2, you coming
What round 2? I just got here.
I'm off after this one,
my brother's home alone.
Then let's go to your house.
He's at the age when
he wants to be alone.
You're such a good sister.
Let's go to our regular spot, or
would you rather cut ties with us?
Cut it right off.
Good, cut him out and go with me.
You've been cut for a while.
Yes.
So-jin, I have something to tell you.
All right, fine, I'll come.
Wow.
Tripping is ingrained in your DNA.
- Hey.
- Cheers!
It's been so long.
It's still here.
Heater…
So-jin.
Yeah?
Come sit here.
Why? What is it?
So-jin.
I'm…
getting married.
What? Married?
Why are you getting married?
With who?
She's a pianist.
Wedding is at your hotel on the 31st.
We haven't dated that too long.
It's at my hotel and you never told me?
He wants you to sing there.
Sing? Screw you.
So-jin, do me this favor.
You have to be very cautious.
They said to go around
even a familiar road
Why would you go around?
The road, well, it's a winding road!
Whoosh! It's curved like that.
Look, she's tying her hair.
Damn, we're in for it now.
We're out of booze.
You should stop, you're drunk.
It's all right, there's
nothing else to drink.
Of course there is.
Oh my!
You up?
You're in better shape than I thought.
You thought wrong,
everything is spinning.
We barely stopped you from
drinking the snake juice last night.
What are you going to do?
I have to leave for
a morning live show.
Who cares, you won't drive me anyways.
I'll at least walk you out.
Is it for real?
Huh, what is?
You getting married.
I wouldn't joke about such a thing.
We've always been like that.
Always joking, kidding around.
True.
We tried hard not to cross the line.
There were always girls who
wanted to cross that line.
Who?
Guest vocalist Yoo-sun,
bassist Young-mi,
and Jin-gyung.
Hey, they all quit the band!
They gave up when you
didn't give them any mind.
Do you know how annoying that is?
They confessed their
feelings for you to me.
What can I do?
I'll come see you at the hotel.
I got a few things to discuss too.
See you.
Asshole.
Sir, could you turn off the radio?
So-jin?
You're up early.
I was heading out to work.
In the same clothes from yesterday?
Tell me if you're
pulling an overnighter.
Going to practice?
Honey ran out, so I made
you some sugar tea.
I wanted to be the pretty seahorse.
But she stole my role.
She's a thieving bitch.
That thief will steal it, hide it.
Mom.
You know, I lost this necklace
but my boss found it for me.
He has something else to steal.
No, it's not like that.
There are good people in the world too.
That punk, he's trying to steal
such a beautiful girl.
Mom, can you call me Lee-young?
Lee-young? My daughter's Lee-young too.
I am your daughter.
Actor, Kwon Sang-woo,
that's Kwon Sang-woo.
Hello, Mr. Kwon Sang-woo,
thank you for coming.
Ah, yes.
- My apologies, I made a mistake.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
Bring some complimentary dishes.
You're Kwon Sang-woo?
Enjoy your meal.
You're a better businessman
than I thought.
It's looking good now.
Speaking of which,
now is the perfect time.
You'll maximize the profit if you
sell it while the business is good.
Let's give our shareholders a
nice gift at the board meeting.
When we merge with East
Chain, the stock will soar,
everyone will make a mint.
The sale will help
your next business too.
It's not all about money,
I want to use my degree…
Yeah, I know.
Your father wanted to let
you start an art business,
and hire a businessman
to run the hotel.
I have a lot of respect for him.
I don't remember him ever loving me,
so I have no respect for him.
You didn't know him.
His most prized treasure
was a drawing you gave
him that he kept in his safe.
I'm a civil servant!
Greatest Quotes
To die proudly when it is no
longer possible to live proudly.
Friedrich Nietzsche
Pharmacy
Ouch!
If you…
take a lot of sleeping
pills, I do mean a lot,
are there any side effects?
Could someone die?
Can't die from taking a lot.
But it'll result in sleep disorders,
increased intraocular pressure,
difficulty urinating, glossitis,
and damage stomach and other organs,
and live rest of your life
in a vegetative state.
I see.
Thank you!
50 cents.
Which pesticide would you like?
Well…
For suicide?
Nowadays, you can't
overdose on pesticides.
You'll just throw up everything
until you throw up your organs.
But you still won't die.
Who said I was going to eat it?
Then I suggest…
taking rat poison.
Why is it so hard to die, dammit!
Shit, I almost died…
Doctors like him are hard to find.
It's not that.
I'm looking for someone who
is family-oriented and can cook.
What if he cooks well
but chews like a cow?
Don't get me started.
Even if it was Gordon Ramsay,
I hate men who chew like a cow.
1) Chew like a cow X
2) Chugging coffee
3) Cook well
I overheard in the washroom.
Give him this.
How to win over women.
Here…
our captain wrote these tips for you.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Evening.
Ms. Eun-su.
Did you wait long?
Yes.
Hey, So-jin.
Yeah, Seung-hyo.
When are you free this week?
This week?
We should grab a bite with my fiancée.
Well, I'm pretty busy.
Since you're busy, tell me
when you're free, got it?
Okay.
Let's meet up.
Christ…
I really wanted to meet you.
He talked a lot about you.
Nice to meet you too, Young-joo.
I guess Australians greet differently.
You're having an
international marriage.
- Shall we order first?
- Sure.
Excuse me.
You know what I want.
- Lasagna.
One lasagna and…
truffle oil pasta for me.
And for my darling,
- truffle creamy mushroom risotto.
- Truffle creamy mushroom risotto.
That'll be all.
Thank you.
Didn't you hate the
gasoline smell of truffle?
It turned into an acquired taste.
You wouldn't even sit
beside me when I ate it.
You used to hate it? I didn't know.
At this rate, you'll eat
engine oil risotto too.
Sorry, I need to take this call.
Okay.
Yes, of course.
To be honest, she's
been acting cold lately.
She's suddenly sensitive
and has tantrums.
I have no clue why.
Pre-wedding jitters?
Huh?
Brides get depressed and
anxious just before wedding.
Is that serious?
I haven't experienced it myself,
but that's my guess.
Could you do me a favor
and meet with her alone?
Me?
Yes.
Why should I?
Sorry.
No thanks.
Staycation my ass.
Got money to burn?
I don't deserve this, I really don't.
I can't die living in the gutter.
I'll at least die luxuriously.
Hotel.
Let's go to a hotel.
I'll stay at a hotel and
jump off the ledge!
Okay!
Ma'am! I'm moving out.
No, moving out for good.
- Don't ever call...
- Hello?
Hello, madam.
Yeah, what?
How are you?
Something came up
and I need to move out.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you for everything.
- A lot of people are interested.
Do I have any deposit remaining?
Not sure.
Look over here.
This way please!
Please wait at the front desk!
Can I help you check in?
I made a reservation, Kang Jae-yong.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Ah, wait.
Sorry, but can I get a higher floor?
As high as possible.
Pardon?
It's… a view thing.
Is this free?
Hello, wake-up call service.
What time should I wake you?
Hello… 9:30 please.
Right, 9:30 in the morning?
Yes…
- One second…
- Yes?
What happens if you call me,
and I don't wake up
or pick up the phone?
Then we will knock on your door.
What if I still don't wake up?
Sorry?
Sorry, it's my first time at a hotel.
It's all right, sir.
Then I'll wake you up
tomorrow morning at 9:30.
Have a nice day.
Yes, thank you.
Please wake me up.
On the last day of the year.
I will end my life at this hotel.
I've never had any luck.
I'm tired of being a
failure and getting rejected.
I'm a worthless human being.
I am a useless piece of flesh,
who's done nothing good for this world.
Goddammit!
This bed is really nice.
This is your wake-up
call, good morning.
Hel… hello, yes, good morning.
It's 9:30, are you awake?
Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
Let me give you a riddle to
prevent your brain from dying.
I'm dying?
Sorry about that.
So that your brain cells stay awake.
Yes, sure.
What do you call a
fish wearing a bowtie?
Call me with the answer
by tomorrow morning.
Thank you and have a nice day.
You're saying he came
here to commit suicide?
Guest services informed
me that the guest in 1739
made some odd inquiries.
What's his itinerary?
He's checking out on January 1st.
Then he might really do it
on the last day of the year.
Could he be…
a consumer from hell?
Don't we just need to make him leave?
Let him die elsewhere.
Do you have any plans to kick him out?
We can pay him to walk out of here.
Can you use your own money to do that?
You don't know what they're like.
I believe that we have
the responsibility
to provide the best
service to all our guests.
Let's try our best to stop him.
Captain Park, can you retrace
his movements until now?
Yes, sir.
Ms. Baek Lee-young.
You did a good job.
Please tell the guest services
to keep an eye on him.
He's a good swimmer.
Please keep me posted
on his whereabouts.
Will do.
13-nothing.
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna confess my
feelings to Ah-young.
It's Christmas eve.
It's the perfect backdrop, bang, bang!
It'll be a Christmas nightmare to her.
You like her too, right?
As a friend, I don't
want to see you get hurt.
Yeah?
Then confess your love too.
We can both get rejected.
Then we can get over her together.
Should we?
I'm in too.
What the hell?
You were into her too?
I just think it'll be fun.
I'll do it if you do it.
Morons.
You coming too?
Why should I?
Score.
When did we come here last?
It's still the same.
Don't men have a special spot
for their first love in their heart?
Where is my spot?
My daughter is getting
married at your hotel soon.
Congrats.
Her name is Young-joo. Young-joo.
That's a pretty name.
Do you know whose daughter she is?
Kang Sang-gyu – 21
Arrested
I'm getting married soon.
I have to get married.
My parents are forcing me
and I can't keep dragging it out.
Congratulations…
on your marriage.
When you get out, marry someone too.
And live a happy life.
But when both of us
become single again…
let's get married.
Don't joke around.
I'm not.
We'll meet again someday.
Be well till then.
She's my daughter, of course.
Indeed.
So silly!
Catch me, catch me if you can!
You're so dead if I get you!
You caught me.
Why are you letting me?
Kill me.
Why would I kill someone so old?
I'm old?
Hey! Wait right there!
You shouldn't have caught me!
Fancy goldfish.
Wrong.
Fish with a bowtie is
called 'sofishticated'!
Ah!
Right!
Since you got it wrong,
you're waking up on your own tomorrow.
Okay, sorry.
You're so gullible.
Should I wake you up
at 9:30 again tomorrow?
Yes, you remembered.
Of course, I got super high EQ and IQ.
- I'll wake you up at 9:30.
- Wait, wait, please.
Can we talk a bit more?
Pardon? Why?
You have a really nice voice.
Do you believe that those with
nice voices are all beautiful?
No, no, no, of course not!
It's all right, I'm also a stunner.
Have a nice day, Merry Christmas!
You're the winner of our
Surprise Christmas contest.
I never signed up for such a thing.
All guests are automatically entered.
What did I win?
What's going on…
♪ You're the most precious ♪
♪ thing in this world ♪
♪ You cannot be replaced ♪
♪ by anything else ♪
♪ Your bright smile ♪
♪ makes me so happy! ♪
Yay!
Thank you.
Lee Gang's concert tickets held
at our hotel on Christmas eve,
as well as a voucher for a free stay
and buffet at our hotel next year.
Next year?
Next year! That's right!
Sir.
Have a wonderful year.
Today is Christmas eve.
I hope you have a gleeful
and unforgettable Christmas.
Merry Christmas!
Hey, hey, how did it go?
Don't cry!
It's okay.
Why is he bowing?
He's smiling.
I'm done.
Are you here to confess too?
To be honest, I don't really like you.
I don't like you either.
Yeah?
I'm glad.
I was worried that
you might be into me.
That's good.
Good job!
Comrades!
Let's go!
- We did it for fun, right?
- Yeah.
Aren't you here to confess too?
No, I just followed them here.
They're a bit weird, but…
they're just weird.
No, they gave me a fun memory.
That's good.
Park Sae-jik!
Merry Christmas.
You too, Merry Christmas.
- "Merry Christmas"?
- What the hell!
I don't know if I can
talk to you like this.
Seung-hyo…
Never mind, forget it.
What is it?
You're making me more curious.
I'm a bit embarrassed to tell you this.
Well…
he hasn't proposed to me yet.
What?
You know how shy he is.
I thought he'd propose if
I mentioned marriage first.
I'm so easy, right?
No way, not at all.
I totally get it.
How's this since he likes pasta.
As a pasta bowl.
He'd like…
this one way more.
Wow.
Sweetie!
You chose something I really like.
How did you know we were here?
I'll be out of your hair then.
Honey, give me a second.
Sure.
Hey!
You can't just leave like that.
Have you had a chat with her?
You were gonna have a
wedding without a proposal?
Proposal?
She did it already.
That's not a proposal.
It means 'propose to me'.
Ah!
What should I do then?
That's up to you.
You look like newlyweds.
Can I recommend something
that will look good for you?
Newlyweds are these two.
I'm so sorry!
Come on…
Oh!
Wait right there.
Do you need help?
Just a bit more!
It's higher than I thought.
You're right.
How's this?
Almost there!
A bit more!
So close!
- That's it!
- Nice!
Here.
Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye
Thank you.
It's Christmas eve, do
you have any plans?
I'm going to the church in a bit.
What about you?
Yeah? I was thinking
of going to one too.
Mr. Kim.
What brings you here?
It's my duty to be here.
Here, congrats.
Thank you.
Aren't you busy nowadays?
Yes, a bit.
I heard you got an offer from KM.
I'm not interested in KM.
Hello.
Way too flashy.
You know how much I like you.
I've always wanted to work
with you for a long time.
Big fish…
needs to swim in a big ocean.
You're the big fish,
Mist is the big ocean.
Have you seen JB's face?
He lives off his face and
it's all scratched up!
What will you do?
It's not like that, sir.
He overreacted and got Gang injured.
First time doing a variety show?
Minor accidents can happen!
Profit losses due to cancelled
schedules this week
can't compare to the little injury
that fake singer is enduring!
Watch your language.
You can insult me all
you want, but not him!
What?
Do you feel like a gangster?
Don't use 'gang' that way!
I'll gang up on him!
Do you know what nickname
Gang hates the most?
It's 'gangster'.
You must be tired, I'll make it short.
Don't make me wait too long.
Gang.
Don't you remember him?
I'm sure he takes care of his family.
What are you saying? Speak your mind.
What's with the outfit?
Are you the singer?
I can't dress shabbily with
so many visitors today.
Why don't you sing on the stage?
Jae-suk gave me this as a gift.
Aren't you Kang Jae-yong?
What? Yeah, that's me.
♪ See the you inside me ♪
♪ When you're tired, ♪
♪ listen to your heart ♪
♪ I'll wake you up ♪
♪ I don't care what people say, ♪
♪ I only have you ♪
♪ The sound inside me, my melody ♪
♪ Listen, listen, listen ♪
♪ Block images of you, ♪
♪ and thoughts of you ♪
♪ Don't worry, let it go ♪
♪ Good bye, good bye, good bye! ♪
Aren't you Kang Jae-yong?
Please leave Hae-sun alone.
I just…
If you show up again,
I'll make you regret it.
♪ …let it go ♪
♪ Good bye, good bye, good bye ♪
♪ When you feel alone, ♪
♪ look in the mirror ♪
♪ Feel the real you! ♪
♪ Can't see the road ♪
♪ Where could it be? ♪
♪ Follow your dreams ♪
♪ further and further ♪
♪ Further and further ♪
♪ Oh, come, all ye faithful, ♪
♪ joyful and triumphant! ♪
♪ Oh, come ye to Bethlehem ♪
Let us pray.
As the saint became a human
through the angel's knowledge,
I pray for grace leading to the glory
of resurrection through
the saint and the cross.
- Amen.
Let's share our peace greetings.
Peace be with you.
When did you last come to church?
It's been a while.
I never liked going alone.
How was it today?
Sitting and standing,
standing and sitting.
It was hard.
Yeah.
The pew was cramped, cold,
hard and uncomfortable.
Totally different from our hotel.
You're right.
But it was nice to sing
the hymn 102 with you.
Good thing it was an even number.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Do you have any traumas?
I don't have any.
You'll return to the stage one day?
I do have an audition
soon but I'm nervous.
You'll do well, don't give up.
Thank you.
I promise to come watch
when you're on the stage.
You can drop me off here.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you too.
♪ Oh darling, are you leaving? ♪
♪ Early morning starlight ♪
♪ falls on white snow ♪
♪ Are you leaving behind ♪
♪ your footprints? ♪
♪ Myeongdong street ♪
♪ on a Christmas night ♪
♪ Numerous couples, who ♪
♪ are they trying to annoy? ♪
♪ Memories suddenly begin to dance ♪
♪ I want to see you, ♪
♪ my beautiful dear ♪
♪ Come back to my palace ♪
♪ My ship that leaves ♪
♪ when the winds blow ♪
♪ Memories suddenly begin to dance ♪
♪ My reflection on show window ♪
♪ It's sub-human, unbelievable ♪
♪ I just stare into full moon ♪
♪ up on the night sky ♪
Merry Christmas, sis!
Don't drink too much
and come home soon.
Let's be happy!
Huh?
Hey!
Hey, wake up!
Excuse me! Hey!
Dammit…
Are you alright?
Sae-jik!
Hey, Sae-jik! Park Sae-jik!
Are you okay?
What happened?
I'm all right.
He…
Thank you so much! Thank you!
My brother would have
died if it wasn't for you.
You're a lifesaver.
I'm glad I found him early.
Stop crying…
Can I give you a riddle?
Absolutely!
Where do ghosts go to sail?
Where do ghosts go… I think I get this.
Does it start with 'Lake'?
Yes.
Lake Boo!
No, the answer is Lake Eerie.
- Lake Eerie.
- Yup.
Can you tell me your name?
I'm Kang Jae-yong.
I'm sorry, but my name
is Wake-Up Call 6.
I'm not human, I'm an AI.
Right, I see.
Sorry, but you've been fooled.
I am human.
Come on!
As per our regulations,
call me Wake-Up Service.
Jeez.
Do you get a lot of rude patrons?
Yes, I do.
A guest requested
a 6:30 call yesterday,
and when I called him, he lashed out.
So, I didn't call him this
morning and he bitched…
I hope those people would stop coming.
I think I'd be good at this job.
Male wake-up service sounds good.
You're kind and have a nice voice.
Maybe in my next life.
So sad.
The songs are getting more mature.
It's good.
He went through a lot.
His parents kicked him out for
dropping out of med school to sing,
band got disbanded,
got into an accident
after debuting solo.
You're crying again.
This song is really good.
Renew his contract already.
So many agencies are after him.
I don't know.
It feels like I'm keeping
him in a small pond.
What are you talking about?
He only got this far because of you.
You sold your house and
worked as a driver for him.
I have to go somewhere,
could you come with me?
Why not?
I come here every year on this day.
I used to come with my
wife until 4 years ago.
I proposed to her here.
Even after a big argument,
we'd come here and
everything would be okay.
She said to me once,
she wanted to marry me
again in the next life.
I said I'd like that too.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I understand what you're saying,
I need some time to think.
You are assigned to lower
floors from tomorrow.
Someone else will clean CEO's suite.
Ms. Baek Lee-young.
You came to work today?
Don't you have an audition?
Well…
Let's go, you still have time.
Please let me go.
No, I won't.
Wait a minute! Wait!
I can't audition in this.
Looks like you're ready.
She's taking rest of the day off!
♪ I can't wait any longer ♪
♪ I've desperately waited ♪
♪ for this moment ♪
♪ Shake off the fear ♪
♪ and I will go my way ♪
♪ Deep and dark past days ♪
♪ Even the high wall that blocked me ♪
♪ Don't scare me anymore ♪
♪ I will fly away ♪
♪ Hold your breath and look at me ♪
♪ I'll show you my everything ♪
♪ The real me that was kept away ♪
♪ Run fast! Fly high! ♪
♪ I won't stop again ♪
Ms. Baek Lee-young!
You were like a different person.
I'm sure there'll be good news.
No, sir.
You've never seen an audition.
I've done it hundreds of times.
I know it right away when
I don't get the part.
I just did my best.
Anyways, thank you
for bringing me here.
But boss…
don't worry about me anymore.
Ms. Baek.
Please!
Stay there.
Boss…
I'm a contract worker.
I can get fired for leaving my post.
Remember you asked
me if I had any traumas?
People like me can't have traumas.
Because…
we cannot afford to.
Even or odd, I can't just change it.
I just accept it and live with it.
Do you think she'll like it?
It's beautiful.
She's here.
Looks so good.
Have a bite.
Sure.
Types of Proposals Women Hate
Ring in Food.
Could be worst day
To Ruin Your Proposal Part 2.
Public Proposal Adds Pressure
Seung-hyo
Hello?
What…
is this?
♪ I love you so much ♪
♪ You're my everything ♪
♪ I promise to always love you ♪
♪ I love you so much ♪
♪ Always stay with me ♪
♪ I'll always be a light by your side ♪
What's wrong? Don't you like it?
Thank you, sweetie.
Is this why you've been so down lately?
Yeah.
You've ruined my first kiss.
I can't wash the feeling away.
So wet and sticky.
You know how grateful I am.
Also…
when you find a girl you like,
don't hesitate, otherwise…
Have you heard of slow mail?
It's this mail box.
It's an ordinary mail
box here in Jumunjin.
But when you send a letter…
it will be delivered a year later.
Hey, was there any mail for me?
Like a postcard!
I put it on your table.
It's really here, no way!
Don't look, go away.
What did you write? Let me peek.
Then show me yours.
Not gonna show you, check it next year.
- Show me!
- No!
My dear friend, So-jin
When you receive this postcard,
you wouldn't be single, right?
I hope you're in a
beautiful relationship!
With someone amazing.
- I'll always cheer you on!
- Seung-hyo
You have to save me!
You keep asking me to save someone.
Who's going to save me?
Please?
You want me to steal your postcard?
It's not stealing,
more like recovering.
Please.
Merger Review
They're not honoring current
employees' promotions.
Shouldn't you let them handle it?
Termination or re-training…
It's better to raise the price and
let them deal with minor issues.
Replace them with better candidates
Please renegotiate so
that no one gets laid off.
Hey man.
I called for you but you didn't answer.
Did you?
I didn't hear you.
Is that a contract from Mist?
Are you spying on me?
I just noticed it, sorry.
Let me ask you a question.
What's a good profit split
with the management?
I'm just asking for your opinion.
Don't ever yield, give them 5%.
5%?
Isn't that too little?
Tell them to forget
it if they don't like it.
Get them to buy you a new ride.
Can I do that?
Of course you can.
You're not the same Lee Gang as before.
Play hardball!
Thanks dude.
You can't look at this!
Okay.
- Don't look.
- I won't.
Who's the hottest singer this year?
Of course, it's Lee Gang.
He's topped the music charts
with every new release since
'Every Couple' last August.
There are rumors that he'll
be joining Mist Entertainment.
Let's listen to 'I Shouldn't Call'
What is it?
that's topping the charts.
Got something to say?
Did you send him this contract?
Yes, I did, so?
Shouldn't you have given it
to me since I'm his manager?
He wanted it, go ask him.
Gang…
hates variety shows.
So don't book him too many of those.
And Gang…
gets pissy when he's writing.
His songs have their own color,
so don't force him to write them.
And Gang…
looks like a city boy but
has tastebuds of a kid.
If you tell him that it's good for him…
he'll refuse once,
but he'll eat it if you're persistent.
Please take good care of him.
♪ Did you even love me? ♪
♪ You'll completely ♪
♪ erase all our memories? ♪
♪ I must not be in your heart anymore ♪
♪ Please look at me ♪
♪ Please look back at me ♪
What happened? Did you retrieve it?
'I wonder where we would
be when you read this.'
Sae-jik!
Did I confess to you?
If I haven't done so and just
burning a hole in my heart…
I told you to rip it up right away!
You're tearing up my heart!
You're so dead!
So-jin.
What?
You'll meet someone better.
Love you.
What the heck?
Dang it…
Hello.
Hello!
Can I help you with that?
No, it's all right.
Here, let me try.
It's not Saturday…
Sorry, it's just that I see you often…
I don't know what I'm doing every week.
Thank you so much.
A year went by so fast.
Take care.
Attention! Salute!
Loyalty!
At ease.
What are you doing?
Sae-jik!
You're our only hope,
we're going to root for you!
Didn't you always?
Not swimming!
Ah-young!
Be totally honest.
About what?
I never lie.
You like Ah-young.
What?
We already know!
So what?
What do you have to do with it?
We can't stand her dating some loser.
She's interested in you,
but since you don't show it…
She's getting tired of waiting.
So what then?
So we told her on your behalf.
Told her what?
We told her that you
wanted to meet with her.
What?!
We hinted to her that you might…
Confess your love on the
cloud bridge after school.
Yes!
I'm done with you all!
What should we tell her then?
That you changed your mind?
I went back to that lake.
I had a long chat with your wife.
And she told me,
that she knew a lot about me…
and she couldn't leave you
because you're such a kid.
So I proposed something to her.
That I'll raise you until the end
and turn you into an adult.
And that I'll send you back
to her in the next life.
Then she answered.
- She did?
- Yes.
Snow.
Snowing on the last day will mean
that she has accepted my proposal.
Look at this!
Your smile brings back your old self.
Okay.
If it doesn't snow,
then I'll shut up and leave you alone.
Agree?
Agreed.
Why did you send Ms.
Baek to another floor?
There are malignant
rumors about you, boss.
Me?
Someone witnessed her
riding in your vehicle.
Can't I not give an employee a lift?
Even if you offered, she
should have refused.
I hear there is a gold digger among us.
Everyone says it's you.
Where there's smoke, there's fire.
Some people are calling you immoral.
I'm immoral?
Yes, I'm not only telling you as
a VP but also as your relative.
Be careful.
What if this puts the merger
with East Chain at risk?
- Is that her?
- Oh my…
Can't trust her looks.
If you have something to say!
Stop whispering and say it to my face!
- Thank you.
It's December 31st,
last day of the year.
How was this year for you?
It was filled with bittersweet moments,
Seung-hyo's wedding
and plenty of regrets,
but on the other hand, it
was a year that allowed you
to become stronger.
You lacked courage
to confess your love,
you were mean to others
in the heat of competition,
you were burdened with
responsibilities for your family,
but pat yourself in the back,
and tell yourself 'you did well today.'
I hope you are happier in the new year.
Let me introduce myself
properly, I'm Lee Jin-ho.
Dear Dad
Merry Christmas
I want to be an awesome
hotelier like you.
Oh man.
Excuse me!
Could you help me?
No, push it, wait, pull it!
I'm so sorry!
Thank you
You are a hero
Thank you for saving
my precious brother.
You're our hero – Park So-jin
He's here, Sae-jik is here.
I might fall for him.
- Did he confess?
- I'm not sure.
Sir.
It's time to leave, sir.
Has East Chain accepted our
request regarding the employees?
I asked them to keep even
the contract workers…
but nothing yet.
Can you give this to the
wake-up service agent?
She'll know if you tell her it's
from room 1739's Kang Jae-yong.
Nice to see you.
It's been a while.
Hello.
Our next CEO.
Not yet!
Hello.
We'll soon begin the
shareholders' meeting,
please take your seats.
Dude.
Huh?
Yeah…
I think you should stop
driving this car from today.
Oh…
Okay.
Sure.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
What about me then?
Mist got you a new car?
What Mist?
Have a seat.
I signed it already,
have a read and sign it.
You…
didn't sign with Mist?
Are you nuts?
Why would I work with a prick like Kim?
He has no interest in music,
and only cares about money.
Don't you remember how
much he looked down on me?
Profit losses can't compare
to the little injury
that fake singer is enduring!
You can insult me all
you want, but not him!
Do you feel like a gangster?
Please don't call him
I still can't forget how he
insulted me while I was down.
A simple apology could
have gone a long way.
Why didn't you tell me?
I knew you couldn't hide it,
that snake Kim would have clued in.
Now it's all up to you,
or I'll get buried.
If you get buried,
I'll dig you back up.
Don't be gross, no touching!
We'll be late, let's go!
Okay.
You said 5% is good, right?
That was with… Mist…
You told me to play hardball.
Okay!
As long as I'm with you.
I increased it a bit.
Please welcome the bride!
You have to walk me when I get married.
No doubt.
Someone was clenching onto you before.
I don't see her anymore,
so I guess she let you go.
Now that you met someone nice,
she must be in a better place.
Groom, Son Seung-hyo
and bride, Kim Young-joo
are here today to exchange their vows,
and to promise and respect each other
no matter what difficult
situations may rise,
and to get through together
with love and knowledge.
You are here to witness
their covenant to
establish the marriage.
Do you, Son Seung-hyo, and
Kim Young-joo, take to be
lawful couple to have and to
hold, from this day forward,
for richer, for poorer, in
sickness and in health,
until death do you part?
- I do!
The two have united as husband and wife
in front of their families and friends,
and promise to cherish each
other until death do them part.
♪ I don't know since when, ♪
♪ but I've kept you in my heart ♪
♪ Good bye other loves ♪
♪ I will only love you ♪
♪ from today ♪
♪ When you came to me, ♪
♪ I was awkward about ♪
♪ my own feelings, ♪
♪ and if I revealed my feelings, ♪
♪ I was afraid you might run away ♪
♪ Can you accept my love? ♪
♪ If you don't like me, ♪
♪ I may be hurt ♪
♪ But should I still confess to you? ♪
♪ I don't know since when, ♪
♪ you creeped into my heart ♪
♪ But there's another farewell ♪
Winter Break
That is all!
Go on, what did you want to tell me?
I was warming up at the pool
when these guys came by.
- They saluted me.
- That idiot.
So what did you want to tell me?
I like you.
Like who?
Lim Ah-young.
I barely heard you.
I like you, Lim Ah-young!
Go out with me!
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Status check on the 1739 guest.
All good, we're cleaning his room.
He's currently out for a bit.
Check if he left a suicide note.
We just have to get through
today, so stay on your toes.
Check the trash bin.
Trash bin is clear.
Okay, I think our plan worked.
Yes, winning the Christmas contest,
and having him save
someone at the pool did it.
Good job, everyone.
Don't let your guard down
until he checks out.
Security office.
What?
Okay, understood.
I'll let her know right away.
Yes, got it!
Please give a big round of applause
to the newlyweds when they bow!
Bride and groom! Bow!
No wonder good things
kept happening to me!
This is from the guest in room 1739.
There's a card too.
Send the security to the rooftop
before anything bad happens.
He took the elevator 5 and headed
to the rooftop from the 25th floor.
Dammit…
Hello?
Hello, do you remember my voice?
Yes…
You're the wake-up call.
Yes, I got your gift.
I called to thank you for it.
I just passed on a gift I received.
No need to thank me.
But I've never received such a gift.
Well, you woke me up every day.
That's just my job though.
- Oh my!
- Don't come close!
Don't come any closer!
Leave me alone…
I have to hang up now.
You don't have to wake me up anymore.
Wait, wait a sec!
Can you talk to me for a bit?
No, thank you.
I have nothing else to say.
When I check out tomorrow,
I have nothing and nowhere to go.
This is where my life ends.
Could you listen to me for a moment?
I listened to you, will
you do the same for me?
Whenever you called, I
wondered who you were.
To be honest,
I was going to jump
off the ledge today too.
Repetitive work and
no one to comfort me.
Next year would be the same,
and I thought I'd rather not see 2022.
Then I ran into someone
who thought like me.
I was really happy
on the phone with you.
I was thankful for the
gift and it made my day.
So, I thought that I would
do anything to help him.
Today,
I will jump off with you.
What?
I'll hold your hand on the way to hell.
I'll jump off with you
we can go together.
Wait! Hold on!
Don't do it, please don't jump.
Why not?
What if people sleep in
because you can't call them?
That's fine.
The person I wanted to wake
up said he didn't need me.
Let's go.
Wait.
Just wake me up tomorrow at 9:30.
Why the change of heart?
I just want to hear the wake-up call.
Thank you.
No, I'm the one thankful.
My legs are shaking.
Mine too.
Wait, wait.
Careful, careful.
I almost really died.
I was worried you might really
want to jump off with me.
I'm afraid of heights.
Same here!
Next up is the opening speech
from CEO of Hotel Emross.
Hello, I'm the CEO of
Hotel Emross, Kim Yong-jin.
My boiler at home burst recently.
I had to stay at our hotel
suite with employee discount,
and had to stay a month
Living in the hotel, I started
seeing things differently.
And I started feeling something
that I've never felt
towards this hotel before.
And I found something my father
had put away in the safe.
Apparently, my childhood dream
was to become a hotelier.
This is the way I want
to follow my dream
alongside all employees
at Hotel Emross.
I will protect Hotel Emross,
and protect employees
who protect Hotel Emross.
I will nullify the merger
with East Chain.
You'll go down for this!
Hotel Emross!
Doesn't only belong to you and I.
It belongs to all our
employee and our guests.
Thank you.
Hey! Kim Yong-jin!
Odd Floors Only
Hello.
Is that the CEO?
He's gorgeous.
Hello.
I came back to celebrate
the New Year with you.
Can we talk outside for a moment?
People are calling me gold digger.
They're calling me immoral.
Gold digger and immoral
aren't a bad combo.
You're right.
It's a fantastic combo.
Even.
So-jin!
Why are you here?
The bride didn't run off, did she?
No, I was worried about you.
Young-joo was worried and
told me to check up on you.
Why?
You just ran off.
Did you think I would jump?
No… I was just worried.
- Seung-hyo.
- So-jin.
You first.
No, you first.
I'll be honest with you
while we're in the elevator.
Only until the elevator stops.
Okay.
I used to like you.
I was going to tell you many times…
I must have overthought it.
'Why should I be the one to tell him?'
'Wouldn't he tell me first one day?'
These thoughts made me
lose courage.
But now I get it.
I was selfish and dishonest.
I was also selfish and dishonest.
But I don't think we were unfortunate
because we didn't express our feelings.
I was happy to be by your
side for 15 years as your friend.
So-jin.
I want you to congratulate me.
Will you?
Congrats on getting married.
It's the truth.
You'll be happy.
Thanks.
You'll be happy too.
So-jin, you're still alive.
Did you run off because
you got jealous?
So-jin, doesn't it feel like
our son is getting married?
Let's follow them on their honeymoon.
Let's see how their first night goes.
Aren't you Sae-jik?
What are you doing?
Sae-jik!
I didn't see that, all right?
Okay.
One man…
- to another.
- To another.
I was overjoyed
to chit chat with you
on the phone
about this and that
every day
Talking about
where to eat,
which movies to watch,
and we just might
date like everyone else
I dared to confess
I was mistaken
It was a crush
I'm sure it was love
by the way you looked at me
I was just a friend
A word I despise
Just a really good guy friend
Friendzoned, nothing more
10! 9!
8! 7! 6!
5!
4! 3!
2!
1!
Sorry, sorry.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Let me introduce myself
properly, I'm Lee Jin-ho.
Do you know why I had
so many blind dates here?
So-jin.
Will you go on a blind date with me?
DIRECTED BY KWAK JAE YONG
I love you, mom.
I'll be here a bit more.
Enjoy your honeymoon.
Okay.
How can you say 'I love you' all day?
You said it over 30 times today!
Is it a new trauma?
Or do you have dementia?
Yes, I have dementia!
My cognitive function
for love is broken.
You're the only one
who can fix it, only you!
How about a kiss here?
It's not in the script.
Hello! Good morning, wake-up service.
How was your sleep?
Yes, it was great.
I feel really great.
You don't sound it.
You fell asleep on the
desk again, didn't you?
You promised me not to do that again…
No, I keep my promises.
You're wiping your drool.
And a Post-it is still
on your left cheek.
Not there.
Over your left shoulder.
What do you see?
I see a very beautiful morning.
So-jin, I got an offer
from a famous hospital.
And?
We were in the elevator
heading to the basement.
Do you know what I did?
I refused the offer.
Because it was a base-pay-ment.
Now I get it.
I knew you'd get my jokes.
No, I see why you've been
rejected over and over again.